{
    "decks": [
        {
            "name": "kj",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "front": "sd",
                    "back": "dfg",
                    "n": 0,
                    "ef": 2.5,
                    "i": 0,
                    "last_studied": 1685831647.839605
                },
                {
                    "front": "gr",
                    "back": "dsc",
                    "n": 0,
                    "ef": 2.5,
                    "i": 0,
                    "last_studied": 1685831651.397608
                },
                {
                    "front": "tjy",
                    "back": "dw",
                    "n": 0,
                    "ef": 2.5,
                    "i": 0,
                    "last_studied": 1685831653.890927
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "oij",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "front": "e",
                    "back": "hj",
                    "n": 1,
                    "ef": 2.6,
                    "i": 1,
                    "last_studied": 1685831722.039194
                },
                {
                    "front": "iudbfg",
                    "back": "df",
                    "n": 1,
                    "ef": 2.6,
                    "i": 1,
                    "last_studied": 1685831761.149642
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "iuht",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "front": "fg",
                    "back": "dw",
                    "n": 1,
                    "ef": 2.5,
                    "i": 1,
                    "last_studied": 1685945056.758934
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "ibu",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "front": "ef",
                    "back": "f",
                    "n": 0,
                    "ef": 2.5,
                    "i": 0,
                    "last_studied": 1685831687.972071
                },
                {
                    "front": "sdf",
                    "back": "bbb",
                    "n": 0,
                    "ef": 2.5,
                    "i": 0,
                    "last_studied": 1685831691.936959
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "s",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "front": "fuck",
                    "back": "duck",
                    "n": 1,
                    "ef": 2.6,
                    "i": 1,
                    "last_studied": 1685944924.894401
                },
                {
                    "front": "back",
                    "back": "frack",
                    "n": 1,
                    "ef": 2.6,
                    "i": 1,
                    "last_studied": 1685944926.7467039
                },
                {
                    "front": "stack",
                    "back": "pack",
                    "n": 1,
                    "ef": 2.6,
                    "i": 1,
                    "last_studied": 1685944928.304287
                },
                {
                    "front": "yuck",
                    "back": "stuck",
                    "n": 1,
                    "ef": 2.6,
                    "i": 1,
                    "last_studied": 1685944930.0273228
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}